- You thought you'd gotten
rid of us, didn't you?
But you were wrong old bean,
because we're back with a vengeance.
- God save the Queen, my son.
("God Save the Queen")
♪ God save the queen ♪
♪ The fascist regime ♪
♪ They made you a moron ♪
♪ Potential H-bomb ♪
♪ God save the queen ♪
♪ She ain't no human being ♪
♪ There is no future ♪
♪ In England's dreaming ♪
♪ Don't be told what you want ♪
♪ Don't be told what you need ♪
♪ There's no future, no future, ♪
♪ No future for you ♪
♪ God save the queen ♪
♪ We mean it man ♪
♪ We love our queen ♪
♪ God saves ♪
♪ God save the queen ♪
♪ 'Cause tourists are money ♪
♪ And our figurehead ♪
♪ Is not what she seems ♪
♪ Oh God save history ♪
♪ God save your mad parade ♪
♪ Oh Lord God have mercy ♪
♪ All crimes are paid ♪
♪ When there's no future ♪
♪ How can there be sin ♪
♪ We're the flowers in the dustbin ♪
♪ We're the poison in your human machine ♪
♪ We're the future, your future ♪
♪ God save the queen ♪
♪ We mean it man ♪
♪ We love our queen ♪
♪ God saves ♪
♪ God save the queen ♪
♪ We mean it man ♪
♪ And there is no future ♪
♪ In England's dreaming ♪
♪ No future, no future, ♪
♪ No future for you ♪
♪ No future for me ♪
♪ No future, no future, ♪
♪ No future for you ♪
♪ No future, no future ♪
♪ For you ♪
- [Radio DJ] The Sex
Pistol's current record,
God Save the Queen,
is at number one of the
capital headline today,
of the IBA which administers
the Broadcasting Act
has advised us this that
particularly at this time
this record is likely to
cause offense to a number
of her listeners and have
asked us not to play it
in our normal programming.
However, we will be playing this record
with the authorities'
approval at 7:30 PM tonight
on Brian Wolf's open line,
and we'll welcome your views
about the punk rock phenomena,
which this is part of.